weloveservers.net 2015-03-16

# Privacy Policy - We Love Servers

**The Information We Collect**

This notice applies to all information collected on the WELOVESERVERS website, or submitted to WELOVESERVERS at any time through any of our services on the website.

Personally Identifiable Information – When visiting WELOVESERVERS`s Web site and signing-up for or using an WELOVESERVERS powered service, Affiliate Program or Reporting Abuse, you may choose to supply WELOVESERVERS with information that identifies you personally. This information may include your name and contact information, as well as other demographic or commerce related information.

 **Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser‟s “help” file. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don‟t have to enter it more than once.

Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but you will be asked to enter your username and password again every time you closed your browser or your session has timed out.

 **Log Files**

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users‟ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to prevent and block abusers to keep using our services such as members who violates our terms of service.

We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies and log files to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate of usage and volume statistics to determine how our users navigate through our website and to know how many users are using our services demographically.

 **The Way We Use Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself or others to complete the transaction for which it is intended. This may include administering a service such as registration, email, forum, etc., or contacting you if you have indicated your permission to do so by agreeing to accept further notification and service announcement from us on your member profile page. You can choose to opt-out of receiving any further notification from your member profile page. We do not share this information with outside parties without your permission.

 **Communications From The Site**

When we receive email, we use return email addresses to reply with the information requested. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. When supplying contact information to WELOVESERVERS you can indicate your preference if you would like to be contacted to receive information and updates about our services by logging in to your WELOVESERVERS account, going to your member profile page and choose not to receive any further notification emails from us or other information pertaining to WELOVESERVERS.

Information you submit to us will not be used for this purpose unless you indicate this as your preference. When supplying contact information to WELOVESERVERS you can indicate your preference on your members profile page to participate in the WELOVESERVERS program if you would like to receive special offers from other companies that we think may be of interest to you through our periodically newsletter. Information you submit to us will not be used for this purpose unless you elect to participate in the WELOVESERVERS program or otherwise consent.

You will receive a confirmation email from us when placing an order on our site and paying through one of our trusted 3rd parties such as PayPal. They only share back information with us about the transaction such as your name, item ordered, email address, etc.

 **Personally identifiable information:**

WELOVESERVERS does not share, sell, rent, or trade PII with third parties for their promotional purposes except with your consent as described in this privacy policy.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described within this privacy policy without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

 **How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into your password-protected account and selecting to update your Profile or Personal Info. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can also correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

 **Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site

 **Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at support@weloveservers.net

 **Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
